<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><feed xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom' xmlns:openSearch='http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/' xmlns:gsx='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006/extended'><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>speakers</title><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/pub?key=0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc'/><link rel='http://schemas.google.com/g/2005#feed' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic'/><author><name>m.kupriyanov</name><email>m.kupriyanov@googlemail.com</email></author><openSearch:totalResults>25</openSearch:totalResults><openSearch:startIndex>1</openSearch:startIndex><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/cokwr</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 2</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Chris Ramsdale, speakercompany: Developer Programs Engineer, Chrome, speakerabstract: Chris Ramsdale has worked extensively in mobile, starting as a Software Engineer at Motorola in 1997, and then joining local start ups as a Tech Lead and Product Manager. Chris's current focus at Google is advocating tools, such as Google Web Toolkit, that allow developers to work within this landscape, creating web applications that seamlessly deploy and run within any browser.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/cokwr'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/cpzh4</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 3</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Don Dodge, speakercompany: Developer Advocate, Google Apps, speakerabstract: Don's focus is on helping developers work with Google Apps. Don joined Google after 5 years as a developer evangelist at Microsoft. Don is a veteran of five start-ups including Forte Software, AltaVista, Napster, Bowstreet, and Groove Networks and has been in the software business for more than 25 years. Don spent 5 years at Microsoft working with VCs and start-ups in the greater Boston area.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/cpzh4'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/cre1l</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 4</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Eric Bidelman, speakercompany: Developer Advocate, Chrome, speakerabstract: Eric's work is focused on the Google Data APIs, primarily on the Google Documents List, Google Health, and the Authentication APIs. Prior to Google, Eric worked as a software engineer at the University of Michigan where he designed rich web applications and APIs for the university's 19 libraries. Eric holds a B.S.E in Computer Engineering and a B.S.E in Electrical Engineering from the University of Michigan, Ann Arbor.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/cre1l'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/chk2m</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 5</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Eric Tholomé, speakercompany: Product Management Director, Developer Products, speakerabstract: Eric joined Google Zurich in 2007 as Product Management Director for Europe, the Middle East, and Africa (EMEA) for Apps products including YouTube, Gmail, Calendar and Docs. Since June 2009, he has been Product Management Director of Developer products in Mountain View. Before Google, Eric worked for Handspring and Palm as Product Line Manager for EMEA. Eric has numerous publications to his credit including a pioneering book on MIDI technology, a GSM technology primer for users, and a contribution to a major guide to telephony. Eric graduated from the Ecole Centrale de Paris in 1990 with a degree in Engineering, and obtained a Masters in Electrical Engineering from Stanford University in 1991. He is fluent in English and French.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/chk2m'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/ciyn3</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 6</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Ernest Delgado, speakercompany: Developer Programs Engineer, Chrome, speakerabstract: Ernest works with developer communities around Google Chrome, Google Chrome Extensions and Google Chrome OS. He loves playing with HTML5 features and solving web performance related issues. Prior to Google, he was working as a Front End Engineer at Yahoo! trying to become a JavaScript guru. Ernest is originally from Barcelona and currently resides in San Francisco.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/ciyn3'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/ckd7g</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 7</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Fred Chung, speakercompany: Developer Advocate, Android, speakerabstract: Fred works with Android developers worldwide to realize compelling mobile apps. He also manages the developer advocacy efforts helping mobile developers to monetize with Google's mobile ads products. Before joining Google, Fred was a consultant at Accenture and has held various software engineering positions in the enterprise systems integration area. Fred currently lives in the San Francisco Bay Area with his family.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/ckd7g'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/clrrx</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 8</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Mario Queiroz, speakercompany: VP Product Management, speakerabstract: Mario joined Google in 2005 and is currently leading an emerging web-video product effort at YouTube and the global deployment of Google TV. Previously at Google, Mario led Android product management as well as international product development across 20 R&amp;D centers. Prior to Google, Mario worked at Hewlett-Packard as vice president within a global operations function, which followed engineering and marketing roles in different HP businesses. Mario holds bachelor's and master's degrees in electrical engineering from Stanford University.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/clrrx'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/cyevm</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 9</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Ossama Alami, speakercompany: Developer Advocate, Geo, speakerabstract: Ossama Alami's main focus is Google's Geospatial APIs. He works closely with the developer community in order to help them build applications that integrate with the Google Maps, Google Earth and related APIs. Ossama's past work experience include Oracle, Accenture and CSC.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/cyevm'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/cztg3</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 10</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Patrick Chanezon, speakercompany: Developer Relations Manager, Cloud and Tools, speakerabstract: Patrick Chanezon joined Google in 2005, he manages the Cloud and Tools Developer Relations team in San Francisco. Previously he has been a Developer Advocate, building and growing developer ecosystems for HTML5, OpenSocial, Google Checkout and the AdWords API, and worked as a software architect at Sun Microsystems, AOL, Netscape and Accenture. Visit him on his Twitter stream (@chanezon).</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/cztg3'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/d180g</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 11</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Peter Fernandez, speakercompany: AdMob, speakerabstract: Peter Fernandez is the Head of Latin America for AdMob. At AdMob he has helped dozens of major mobile app developers refine their monetization strategies and maximize their earnings. He is currently working to help Latin American app developers benefit as Google and AdMob merge and improve their ad-monetization offerings.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/d180g'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/d2mkx</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 12</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Ryan Boyd, speakercompany: Developer Advocate, Google Apps, speakerabstract: Ryan's focus is on enabling developers to extend Google Apps and build businesses on top of Google technology. He previously worked on OpenSocial, Google Friend Connect and Google's AtomPub APIs. Prior to joining Google, Ryan worked in higher education as a web architect for RIT's web hosting environment and as web app developer.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/d2mkx'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/cssly</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 13</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Tim Bray, speakercompany: Developer Advocate, Android, speakerabstract: Tim Bray's work is currently focused on the Android platform. A software developer and entrepreneur, he was a co-founder of Open Text Corporation (Nasdaq:OTEX), author of one of the first Web search engines, and co-inventor of XML. He is a popular blogger (tbray.org/ongoing/) and Twitterer (@timbray).</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/cssly'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/cu76f</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 14</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Alexander Ferraz Tabor, speakercompany: CTO and Co-founder, Peixe Urbano, speakerabstract: Alexander Ferraz Tabor is the CTO and co-founder of Peixe Urbano, the first and largest deal-a-day website in Brazil. Alexander has a BS in Computer Science from the University of Southern California.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/cu76f'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/cvlqs</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 15</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Bruno Souza, speakercompany: Application Development Manager, Studio Sol, speakerabstract: Bruno Souza is the application development manager for Studio Sol, a Brazilian company that develops several of the most popular soccer and music-related Orkut applications in Brazil, such as Eu Sou! and Minha Musica, which today are installed in over 34 million Orkut profiles.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/cvlqs'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/cx0b9</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 16</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Cezar Sá Espinola, speakercompany: Web Developer, speakerabstract: Cezar is a software developer currently involved with the development of Google Chrome extensions and web applications. He is the main developer of the Chromed Bird extension that works as a Twitter client and makes use of JavaScript and HTML5 APIs. Recently he has been experimenting with the development of Java and Ruby applications running on Google App Engine.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/cx0b9'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/d9ney</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 17</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Daniel Kafie, speakercompany: CEO, Vostu, speakerabstract: Daniel is the CEO of Vostu, a major social gaming company in Brazil with more than 20 million monthly active users and 200 employees in Sao Paulo, Buenos Aires, and New York. Vostu's signature games, Mini Fazenda and Cafe Mania, are the top 2 games on the Orkut platform. Daniel holds a BA in Economics from Harvard University and an MBA from Harvard Business School where he focused on entrepreneurship.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/d9ney'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/db1zf</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 18</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Eric Acher, speakercompany: Partner, Monashees Capital, speakerabstract: Eric Acher is a Founding Partner at Monashees Capital, a Brazilian Venture Capital firm focused on consumer internet and education technologies. Before founding Monashees, Eric did VC investing in the U.S. and Latin America with General Atlantic. He also worked with strategic planning at Unibanco and strategy consultancy at McKinsey. Eric holds an MBA form the Kellogg School of Management, a Business Administration degree from Fundação Getúlio Vargas and a B.A. from ESPM.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/db1zf'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/dcgjs</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 19</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Humberto Matsuda, speakercompany: VP, Performa Investments, speakerabstract: Humberto Matsuda is a partner at Performa Investimentos, where he is responsible for the management of Venture Capital Funds. Also, he is a member of the Entrepreneurship, Innovation and Seed Capital Committee (CEICS) at the Brazilian Venture Capital Association (ABVCAP). He has over 12 years of industry practice and since 2007 has been focused on managing Venture Capital Funds, primarily on Seed Capital and Early Stage investments.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/dcgjs'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/ddv49</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 20</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Juan Franco, speakercompany: CEO and Founder, Mentez, speakerabstract: Juan Franco has 15 years of experience managing internet companies in Latam, such as VMWare, Salesforce, EMC, etc and founder of Mentez. Mentez has 20M+ users in Brasil that play and enjoy their games. 7 of the Top 10 Games are theirs. Today, Mentez is a major player in the Social Internet in Brasil and Latin America and is now working on building a powerful monetization platform for any virtual content.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/ddv49'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/d415a</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 21</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Marcelo Marzola, speakercompany: Co-Founder and CEO, Predicta/BTBuckets, speakerabstract: Marcelo is the CEO and one of the co-founders of Predicta/BTBuckets. Through its marketing and behavioral targeting offerings, Predicta services clients in over 90 countries worldwide and was recognized in 2009 as one of Brazil's 25 most innovative companies. Marcelo is an Associate Instructor in web analytics at the UBC, Canada, and holds a BSM from IBMEC/Brazil and a Masters in Business Administration from FGV/Brazil.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/d415a'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/d5fpr</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 22</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Marcos Farias, speakercompany: Technology Director, Just Digital, speakerabstract: Marcos is a founding member of Just Digital, a company specializing in web development and integration of Google Search Appliance (GSA). He is the official GSA instructor (including delivering training abroad) as well as a Google Apps instructor and Java developer. He just led the development of a SSO Single Sign On solution in Brazil with a focus on Google Apps. Marcos holds a Bachelor's Degree in Physics from the University of São Paulo (USP).</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/d5fpr'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/d6ua4</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 23</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Otávio Rezende da Silva, speakercompany: Senior Product Manager, Webb, speakerabstract: Otavio has been at Webb since 2001, where he was responsible for the product roadmap and a team of 30 developers specialized in Java, GWT and Supply Chain Management. His major projects include developing Webb's new eProcurement solution and a tool to integrate with different ERP systems. Otavio has a Bachelor's degree in Computer Engineering from PUC-Rio and a Masters in Software Engineering from the same university.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/d6ua4'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/d88ul</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 24</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Phillip Klien, speakercompany: Co-Founder and Chief Innovation Officer, Predicta/BTBuckets, speakerabstract: Phillip is the co-founder of Predicta and BTBuckets. His company was recognized as one of Brazil's 25 most innovative companies in 2009, and has received the 2009 WAALTER award by the Web Analytics Association. He holds a BSM from Tulane University and currently leads the innovation department at Predicta's HQ in São Paulo, Brazil.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/d88ul'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/dkvya</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 25</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Eduardo Thuler, speakercompany: ..., speakerabstract: ...</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/dkvya'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/dmair</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 26</title><content type='text'>speakertitle:  Alex Tabor, speakercompany: ..., speakerabstract: ...</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od7/public/basic/dmair'/></entry></feed>