<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><feed xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom' xmlns:openSearch='http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/' xmlns:gsx='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006/extended'><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>sessions</title><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/pub?key=0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc'/><link rel='http://schemas.google.com/g/2005#feed' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic'/><author><name>m.kupriyanov</name><email>m.kupriyanov@googlemail.com</email></author><openSearch:totalResults>21</openSearch:totalResults><openSearch:startIndex>1</openSearch:startIndex><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/cokwr</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 2</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 29.10.2010, sessiontime: 13:50-14:35, room: 1, product: Android, track: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: Android Ecosystem and What's New, tags: Android, Mobile, Java, sessionspeakers: Tim Bray, sessionabstract: This talk combines an introduction to the Android ecosystem with a description of what's new in it. The ecosystem includes the technology, developer community, Android Market, and of course the huge population of Android users., sessionlink: whats-new-in-froyo-cloud-to-device-messaging, sessionhashtag: #android1</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/cokwr'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/bs9tc</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 3</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 29.10.2010, sessiontime: 14:40-15:25, room: 1, product: Android, track: Android, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Effective UI Design in Android, tags: Android, Mobile, Java, sessionspeakers: Tim Bray, sessionabstract: Good user interfaces and optimized user experiences are important on any device, but are even more important on mobile devices that have limited screen real estate and are being used by people in a hurry. We'll talk about UI and UX design patterns on Android and how to use them to greatest effect., sessionlink: effective-ui-design-in-android, sessionhashtag: #android2</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/bs9tc'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/cre1l</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 4</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 29.10.2010, sessiontime: 15:30-16:15, room: 1, product: Android, track: Android, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Flexible Android Applications: Adapting to Hardware and Locale, tags: Android, Mobile, Java, sessionspeakers: Fred Chung, sessionabstract: Android provides facilities to make flexible applications that work well for everyone on any piece of hardware running Android. This session will cover localization and internationalization, as well as how to write an app that can detect and adapt to the hardware and software resources available to it., sessionlink: flexible-android-applications-adapting-to-hardware-and-locale, sessionhashtag: #android3</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/cre1l'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/bqv8z</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 5</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 29.10.2010, sessiontime: 16:30-17:15, room: 1, product: Android, track: Android, sessiontype: 151, sessiontitle: Building High-Performance Applications, tags: Android, Mobile, Java, sessionspeakers: Tim Bray, sessionabstract: Build Android applications that are smooth, fast, responsive, and a pleasure to use. Also, learn about the tools and techniques we use to track down and fix performance problems., sessionlink: building-better-android-apps-beyond-the-basics, sessionhashtag: #android4</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/bqv8z'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/clrrx</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 6</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 29.10.2010, sessiontime: 11:15-12:00, room: 2, product: Chrome &amp; HTML5, track: Chrome &amp; HTML5, sessiontype: 151, sessiontitle: Enhance Your Browser with Google Chrome Extensions, tags: Chrome, sessionspeakers: Ernest Delgado, sessionabstract: Learn how to use standard web technologies (HTML/JS/CSS) for adding extra functionality to Google Chrome, Chrome OS, or any page on the internet! Give your users things like a tab manager, music player, color picker, you name it!, sessionlink: enhance-your-browser-with-google-chrome-extensions, sessionhashtag: #chrome1</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/clrrx'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/cyevm</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 7</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 29.10.2010, sessiontime: 12:05-12:50, room: 2, product: Chrome &amp; HTML5, track: Chrome &amp; HTML5, sessiontype: 151, sessiontitle: Building for a Faster Web, tags: Chrome, sessionspeakers: Eric Bidelman, sessionabstract: Why should a web app be less performant than a native app? This session will focus on creating the next generation of web applications. We'll look HTML5 features that increase app performance, Chrome Developer Tools to speed development, Native Client for running native C++ in the browser, and Google Chrome Frame to bring these awesome features to users with older browsers., sessionlink: building-for-a-faster-web, sessionhashtag: #chrome2</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/cyevm'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/cztg3</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 8</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 29.10.2010, sessiontime: 13:50-14:35, room: 2, product: Chrome &amp; HTML5, track: Chrome &amp; HTML5, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: HTML5++ - The Future of the Web Now!, tags: Chrome, sessionspeakers: Ernest Delgado, sessionabstract: Have you felt frustrated when you tried to build a complex web app in the HTML 4 era? HTML5 comes to the rescue. Whether you're developing for the desktop or mobile browser, this session will discuss key features for building tomorrow's web apps, today., sessionlink: html5-the-future-of-the-web-now, sessionhashtag: #chrome3</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/cztg3'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/d180g</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 9</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 29.10.2010, sessiontime: 16:30-17:15, room: 2, product: Chrome &amp; HTML5, track: Chrome &amp; HTML5, sessiontype: 151, sessiontitle: So What's A Web App? Introduction to the Chrome Web Store, tags: Chrome, sessionspeakers: Eric Bidelman, sessionabstract: What does it mean to install a web app? This session will give an overview of how to build a beautiful application for the Chrome Web Store, monetize, and distribute it to 70 million users!, sessionlink: so-whats-a-web-app-introduction-to-the-chrome-web-store, sessionhashtag: #chrome4</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/d180g'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/d2mkx</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 10</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 29.10.2010, sessiontime: 17:20-18:05, room: 2, product: Chrome &amp; HTML5, track: Chrome &amp; HTML5, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: OpenID-based single sign-on and OAuth data access, tags: Chrome, sessionspeakers: Ryan Boyd, sessionabstract: A discussion of all the auth tangles you've encountered so far -- OpenID, SSO, 2-Legged OAuth, 3-Legged OAuth, and Hybrid OAuth. We'll show you when and where to use them, and explain how they all integrate with Google APIs and other developer products., sessionlink: openid-based-single-sign-on-and-oauth-data-access, sessionhashtag: #chrome5</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/d2mkx'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/dcgjs</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 11</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 29.10.2010, sessiontime: 11:15-12:00, room: 3, product: App Engine, track: Cloud Platform, sessiontype: 151, sessiontitle: What's new in Google App Engine and Google App Engine For Business, tags: App Engine, sessionspeakers: Patrick Chanezon, sessionabstract: Learn what's new with Java on App Engine. We'll take a whirlwind tour through the changes since last year, walk through a code sample for task queues and the new blobstore service, and demonstrate techniques for improving your application's performance. We'll top it off with a glimpse into some new features that we've planned for the year ahead. This session will include an overview of Google App Engine for Business., sessionlink: whats-new-in-google-app-engine-and-google-app-engine-for-business, sessionhashtag: #appengine1</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/dcgjs'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/b8lvi</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 12</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 29.10.2010, sessiontime: 12:05-12:50, room: 3, product: Google Web Toolkit, track: Cloud Platform, sessiontype: 151, sessiontitle: Google Web Tookit: What it is, How it Works and Deeper Dives, tags: Google Web Toolkit, sessionspeakers: Chris Ramsdale, sessionabstract: If you're like the rest of us, at some point in your web app development you've wondered if there was an easier solution. One that includes built-in debuggers, code refactoring, reliable syntax highlighting, etc. After all, why should the server-side and desktop programmers get all of the good tools? The good news is that with Google Web Toolkit (GWT) you do have access to these tools. And in this session, Chris Ramsdale will get you up and running with GWT, including what it is, how it works, and deeper dives into generators, native Javascript interop, and compiler optimizations., sessionlink: google-web-tookit-what-it-is-how-it-works-and-deeper-dives, sessionhashtag: #appengine2</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/b8lvi'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/ba0fz</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 13</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 29.10.2010, sessiontime: 14:40-15:25, room: 3, product: Google Web Toolkit, track: Cloud Platform, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Building Business Apps using Google Web Toolkit and Spring Roo, tags: Google Web Toolkit, sessionspeakers: Chris Ramsdale, sessionabstract: Who says you can't build rich web apps for your business? Follow along in this session to learn how you can use the latest integrated set of tools from Google and VMware to take your internal business apps into the cloud. We'll cover how to get started using GWT with Spring Roo and SpringSource Tool Suite (STS), as well as the new data presentation widgets and MVP framework that will be available in the 2.1 release of GWT., sessionlink: building-business-apps-using-google-web-toolkit-and-spring-roo, sessionhashtag: #appengine3</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/ba0fz'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/bbf0c</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 14</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 29.10.2010, sessiontime: 15:30-16:15, room: 3, product: BigQuery, Prediction APIs, track: Cloud Platform, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: Storage, Bigquery and Prediction APIs, tags: BigQuery, Prediction APIs, sessionspeakers: Patrick Chanezon, sessionabstract: Google is expanding our storage products by introducing Google Storage for Developers. It offers a RESTful API for storing and accessing data at Google. Developers can take advantage of the performance and reliability of Google's storage infrastructure, as well as the advanced security and sharing capabilities. We will demonstrate key functionality of the product as well as customer use cases. Google relies heavily on data analysis and has developed many tools to understand large datasets. Two of these tools are now available on a limited sign-up basis to developers: (1) BigQuery: interactive analysis of very large data sets and (2) Prediction API: make informed predictions from your data. We will demonstrate their use and give instructions on how to get access., sessionlink: storage-bigquery-and-prediction-apis, sessionhashtag: #appengine4</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/bbf0c'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/ddv49</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 15</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 29.10.2010, sessiontime: 11:15-12:00, room: 4, product: Maps API, track: Google APIs, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Maps API V3: New Features and How to Use them, tags: Maps API, sessionspeakers: Ossama Alami, sessionabstract: The Javascript Maps API v3 is the future of the Google Maps API. Come learn why we built it, how to use it and about some exciting new features not available in V2., sessionlink: maps-api-v3-new-features-and-how-to-use-them, sessionhashtag: #mapsapi</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/ddv49'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/d6ua4</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 16</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 29.10.2010, sessiontime: 12:05-12:50, room: 4, product: Social Web, track: Google APIs, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: The Open and Social Web, tags: Social Web, sessionspeakers: Patrick Chanezon, sessionabstract: This session will cover the latest and most important trends of the Social Web and dive deep into where this is all going, at both technical and conceptual levels., sessionlink: the-open-and-social-web, sessionhashtag: #socialweb</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/d6ua4'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/bl8zb</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 17</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 29.10.2010, sessiontime: 14:40-15:25, room: 4, product: Google Geo, track: Google APIs, sessiontype: 151, sessiontitle: Google Geo: Exciting New Features and Tools, tags: Google Geo, sessionspeakers: Ossama Alami, sessionabstract: Did you know we have an elevation web service? That you can completely restyle the look of the map tiles? How to use Fusion Tables to host and visualize geo data? A session covering new launches across Google's Geo products and some APIs you might not be aware of. Covering Web services, Earth API, New KML Extensions, Maps Styling, Fusion Tables., sessionlink: google-geo-exciting-new-features-and-tools, sessionhashtag: #googlegeo</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/bl8zb'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/bjueu</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 18</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 29.10.2010, sessiontime: 15:30-16:15, room: 4, product: Google Apps APIs, track: Google APIs, sessiontype: 151, sessiontitle: Google Apps APIs, tags: Google Apps APIs, sessionspeakers: Ryan Boyd, sessionabstract: Google Apps APIs: Provisioning, Apps Script, Contacts, Calendar, Mail migration. Focused on SIs+Customers, sessionlink: google-apps-apis, sessionhashtag: #googleappsapis</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/bjueu'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/btodt</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 19</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 29.10.2010, sessiontime: 16:30-17:15, room: 4, product: Google Apps, track: Google APIs, sessiontype: 151, sessiontitle: Google Apps Marketplace - Business and Technical Topics, tags: Google Apps, sessionspeakers: Ryan Boyd, sessionabstract: Google Apps Marketplace - business and technical topics. Focused on ISVs or SIs looking to productize some of their work, sessionlink: google-apps-marketplace-business-and-technical-topics, sessionhashtag: #appengine5</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/btodt'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/bmnjo</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 20</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 29.10.2010, sessiontime: 17:20-18:05, room: 4, track: Google APIs, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: Earn Money from your Mobile App with AdMob, tags: AdMob, sessionspeakers: Peter Fernandez, sessionabstract: We’ll show you different strategies for monetizing your app with AdMob ads and help you figure out how much you can earn. We'll also share enlightening data on the growth of the Android, iPhone and iPad platforms., sessionlink: admob, sessionhashtag: #admob</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/bmnjo'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/djhdx</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 21</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 29.10.2010, sessiontime: 13:50-14:35, room: 5, product: Panels, track: Panels, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: Panel: Social Gaming, Virtual Currency and Ad Campaigns, tags: Panel, sessionspeakers: Eduardo Thuler, Juan Franco, Daniel Kafie, Bruno Souza, sessionabstract: Social games are more than just fun: in recent years they have more than proved their value as a profitable business area. In this panel, you will have the opportunity to listen to what successful social gaming companies in Latin America have to say on social applications and their approaches to monetization such as virtual currency and in-game ad campaigns. Learn from their experience as they share their challenges and success stories in this exciting market., sessionlink: panel-social-gaming-virtual-currency-and-ad-campaigns, sessionhashtag: #panel1</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/djhdx'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/dw4je</id><updated>2010-10-27T23:25:06.648Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 22</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 29.10.2010, sessiontime: 17:20-18:05, room: 5, product: Panels, track: Panels, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: VC Panel: Entrepreneurship, Incubation and Venture Capital, tags: Panel, sessionspeakers: Don Dodge, Eric Acher, Humberto Matsuda, Alex Tabor, sessionabstract: Startups can be built and funded anywhere in the world, not just Silicon Valley. Venture Capital investors are investing in startups globally, and funding incubators to hatch their future investments. Find out how you can get into an incubator, or funded by a Venture Capitalist or Angel Investors. Learn from examples in the USA and hear from local VC investors in this panel discussion. Get your questions answered by real investors., sessionlink: vc-panel-entrepreneurship-incubation-and-venture-capital, sessionhashtag: #panel2</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdGM3ejFLUldvbnhubTVjb1hMZU83Umc/od6/public/basic/dw4je'/></entry></feed>